{
  "mc-questions": [
    {
      "question": "Python is a:",
      "answers": ["Programming language", "Snake", "Dish", "Band"],
      "answer": "Programming language"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a data structure?",
      "answers": [
        "A method",
        "A way to store/organize data",
        "An algorithmn",
        "A way to predict the future"
      ],
      "answer": "A way to store/organize data"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the short hand hexadecimal for this hexadecimal color: #FFFFFF",
      "answers": ["#F", "#FF", "#FFF", "None of the above"],
      "answer": "#FFF"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the original hexadecimal for this shorthand hexadecimal color: #C6C",
      "answers": ["#CC66CC", "#CC6C", "#CCC", "None of the above"],
      "answer": "#CC66CC"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Java?",
      "answers": [
        "A programming language",
        "A coffee shop",
        "A dish",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "A programming language"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is JavaScript basically Java?",
      "answers": [
        "Yes",
        "Its literally Java 2.0",
        "No, they are not the same!",
        "Without a doubt"
      ],
      "answer": "No,they are not the same!"
    },
    {
      "question": "How long has JavaScript been around for?",
      "answers": ["30 years", "10 years", "8 years", "27 years"],
      "answer": "27 years"
    },
    {
      "question": "Python is a:",
      "answers": ["Programming language", "Snake", "Dish", "Band"],
      "answer": "programming language"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does JSE stand for?",
      "answers": [
        "JavaScript encapsulation",
        "JavaScript enviorment",
        "JavaScript engine",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "JavaScript engine"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does NPM stand for?",
      "answers": [
        "No Private Module",
        "No Package Module",
        "Node Package Manager",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "Node Package Manager"
    }
  ],
  "tf-questions": [
    {
      "question": "In JavaScript shift() removes the first element in the array",
      "answers": ["true", "false"],
      "answer": "true"
    },
    {
      "question": "In JavaScript pop() removes the first element in the array",
      "answers": ["true", "false"],
      "answer": "false"
    },
    {
      "question": "In JavaScript the push() adds elements to the end of an array",
      "answers": ["true", "false"],
      "answer": "true"
    },
    {
      "question": "In JavaScript unshift() adds the element to the beginning of the list",
      "answers": ["true", "false"],
      "answer": "true"
    },
    {
      "question": "You get an error when accessing an out-of-bound index in javascript",
      "answers": ["true", "false"],
      "answer": "false"
    },
    {
      "question": "== is equivalent to ===",
      "answers": ["true", "false"],
      "answer": "false"
    },
    {
      "question": "The value of a variable declared const can change its value",
      "answers": ["true", "false"],
      "answer": "false"
    },
    {
      "question": "Classes do not exist in JavaScript",
      "answers": ["true", "false"],
      "answer": "false"
    },
    {
      "question": "Event listeners listen for action only once",
      "answers": ["true", "false"],
      "answer": "false"
    },
    {
      "question": "DRY stands for \"do not repeat yourself\"",
      "answers": ["true", "false"],
      "answer": "true"
    }
  ]
}
